Guide to the Paper Tiger Television Archive, ca. 1981-2014 MSS.276
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Activities
  - Subseries C: Workshops and Conferences
    - Brooklyn Friends School - Media Literacy Workshop, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Class Dismissed - workshop evaluation sheets, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Class Dismissed - workshop - online lesson plan examples, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Class Dismissed - worshop series, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Class Dismissed - workshop series, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Committee leadership training, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Community Media Leadership Institute conference, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Curriculum Development workshop / Youth workshop meeting notes, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 27A)
    - Demo Against Media, Undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Diversity training / race workshop, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Educational Video Center - workshop materials, Undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Fenced Out workshop - outline, Undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Fierce / NNZ at Cypher, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Fierce / NNZ at Cypher, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Final Cut workshop, Undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Final Cut workshop - editings, PTTV evaluations, Undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Final Cut workshop - Final Cut Pro, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Final Cut workshop - Final Cut Pro handouts, Undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Final Cut workshop - Final Cut Pro workshop, Undated (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Freeing the Media - Teach in / Speak out, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Gender Roles workshop, Undated (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Goddard College Summer Program, Undated (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Green Chimneys - research, waivers, and logs, Undated (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Green Chimneys - youth outreach, Undated (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Gulf War Rally - flyers, Undated (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Hands On! Youth, Media, and Activism after Seattle - workshop, Undated (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Independent Features conference, Undated (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Invoices file - Drums Asian Working Class Women and Girls workshop, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Jean Zine - Lower East Side Girls Club - made at PTTV workshop, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Learning Tech Fair, Undated (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Legal Issues for Filmmakers workshop, Undated (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Manhattan Neighborhood Network - youth initiated channel, Undated (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Military Myths - APSC's Counter Recruitment training manual, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Military Myths - Articles and Ads, Undated (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Military Myths - Changing America, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Military Myths - classroom curriculum, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Military Myths - curriculum, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Military Myths - endorser agreements, Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Military Myths - evaluations - screenings and flyers, Undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Military Myths - Interview contacts, Undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Military Myths - Jen with Roots workshop notes, Undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Military Myths - Jen to do (feedback), Undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Military Myths - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Military Myths - outreach, correspondence, evaluation forms, Undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Military Myths - pamphlets, workshop material, curriculum, Undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Military Myths - press releases and questionaire, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Military Myths - Related events, partner organizations, Undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Military Myths - Release forms for interviews, Undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Military Myths - Roots (binder), Undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Military Myths - Roots workshop, Undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Military Myths - Roots schedule, Undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Military Myths - screening locations, Undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Military Myths - stats and alternatives, Undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Military Myths - Stats, recruitment and anti-recruitment material, Undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Military Myths - workshop summary, Undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous seminars, research, lectures, Undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - NAMAC conference, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - NAMAC and media summer program, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - NAMAC - newsletter, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - NAMAC - youth, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - New Neutral Zone Report - workshop, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Next 5 Minutes - conference, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - New York City Grassroots Media conference, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - NFCLP Spring conference, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Oligopoly cards, Undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Open Society Institute U.S. programs, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Paper Tiger TV workshop curriculum, Undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Paper Tiger Productions workshop - evaluations, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Plato Royalty Lecture at Evergreen State College, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - The Point workshop, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Police Accountablilty Project, Undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Press Packet - Occupation and Intervention: perspectives on the Middle East, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Production handouts for workshops, Undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Project Reach, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Queeruption - flyers, Undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Queeruption - Homo economics, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Queeruption - Queeruption Gay Expo, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Queeruption - Tara meeting notes / volunteer sheet, Undated (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Queeruption - Timeline, Undated (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Roots - video open house evaluation, Undated (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Roots - video / media lit resources, Undated (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - "Senses of Home: Dialogue within communities" program - photo, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Social Theory, Politics, and the Arts conference, Undated (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Standing with Palestine project binder, Undated (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Streetwork workshop, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Subcomandante Marcos message, Undated (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - TeacHarlem II at City College of New York, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Training for Transformation workshop, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Truce, Undated (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Truce (Military Myths), Undated (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Union for Democratic Communication conference, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Video Production curriculum, Undated (Box 12, Folder 56A)
    - Workshop curriculum file - learning exercises, Undated (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Workshop curriculum file - loose papers, Undated (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - World Communications conference, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Youth Force, Undated (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Youth Peace Workshop, Undated (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Youth Summit, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - [Flat Box] Self-description cards, Undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Subseries D: Film Festivals and Screenings
    - Access Orbit screenings, Undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Alliance for Community Media screenings, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - American Film Institute video festival, 1988-1994 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - American Museum of Natural History - "Senses of Home" screening, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - "Amerika" screenings, Undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Ann Arbor Film Festivals, Undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Athens Film Festival, 1995-1999 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Atlanta Film and Video Festival, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Atlanta Film Festival, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Austin Gay and Lesbian International Film Festival, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Awards, Undated (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Black Maria Film and Video Festival, Undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Brainwash Movie Festival, Undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Brecht Forum - Military Myths, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Bronx Museum of the Arts, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Brooklyn Art Council (BACA) Annual Film and Video Festival, Undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Brooklyn College screening, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Brooklyn Underground Film Festival, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Canada screening - Smashing the Myths...and Staking a Claim in Cyberspace, Undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Casualties of War - screening info, Undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Chicago International Telvision Competition, 1998-1999, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Cinemambiente Festival, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Conference Screenings, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence regarding screenings, Undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - CYPHER - Fenced Out screening, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Dallas Video Festival - Showdown in Seattle, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Do it Your Damn Self - National Youth Film and Video Festival, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - "Fat is Beautiful" screenings, Undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Feminist Film Festivals, Undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Festivals / Awards, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Festivals not in, Undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Flaming Film Festival, 2002-2005 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Fledgling Film Festival, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Foreign screenings, Undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Fringe Film Festival, 1993-1995 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Gay and Lesbian Film Festivals, 1996, 2000-2003 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Gay and Lesbian Film Festivals, 2004-2006 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Gurl Film Festival, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Hampshire College screenings, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Hamptons International Film Festival - Homecoming Queens, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Hip Hop Odyssey International Film Festival, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Homecoming Queens - screenings, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Hometown Video Festival, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Hometown Video Festival, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Human Rights Watch International Film Festival, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Human Rights Watch International Film Festival - Press Report, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Image News Film / Video Center, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Images Film Festival - Military Myths, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - International Documentary Film Festival - El Tude Verdade, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Ithaca Summer School of the Arts screening - Tara Mateik, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Jeoju International Film Festival - Korea, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Lady Fest - invoice, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Loco Motion International Film Festival, 2003-2004 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Lower East Side Girls Club, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Margaret Mean Film and Video Festival, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Market This! screening, Undated (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Medgar Evers College - screening, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Media Matters, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Military Myths World Premier, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Military Myths screenings, Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Museum of Television and Radio - Fenced Out, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - National Educational Media Network, 1995-1998 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - National Art, Activism, and Analysis tour - Paper Tiger reads Paper Tiger, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - New York City - local screenings, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - New York Free Media Alliance screenings, Undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - New York Lesbian and Gay Film Festival, 1999-2003 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - North Star Fund screenings - Shared Histories, Undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - The Other America Film Festival, Undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Palestine screening - Rock Paper Missiles, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Pandæmonium: Biennial of Moving Images, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Paper Tiger TV course outline, Undated (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Peace and Human Security Media Festival, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Project Reach Youth, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Queer Youth Nation - TV or not TV..., 2002 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - "Race, Crime, and the Media" screening, Undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Recording / Transmission, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Rock Paper Missiles screening, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Rotterdam Film Festival, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - San Francisco International Lesbian and Gay Film Festival, Undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Sarah Lawrence Film and Video Festival, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1982-1983 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1990 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - Screenings - mixed, 1995-1996 (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - Seoul Human Rights Film Festival, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Seoul International Film Festival, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Shedhalle, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Sleeth Gallery, 1996 (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - Subcomandante Marcos, Undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Subverting Media screenings, Undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Summer Screening Series, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Summer Screening Series, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Taos Talking Pictures Festival, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Taos Talking Pictures Festival, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Teen Screen Image Atlanta, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Three Rivers Arts Festival, 1990-1995 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Tribeca Film Festival, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Turning Tragedy into War - MOMA screening, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - USA Film Festival, 1995-1999 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Urban Visionaries Festival, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - VC Film Fest, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Whitney - New American Film and Video Series, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Whitney - PTTV screenings, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - "Propaganda / Whitney" screening, Undated (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Who's Paying the Price screenings, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Women in the Director's Chair - Film and Video Festival, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Woodstock screenings, Undated (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - Youth film festivals, Undated (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Youth Media Arts NYC - Urban Visionaries, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Youth Media Jam, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Miscellaneous screenings and film festivals, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Miscellaneous screenings and film festivals, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Miscellaneous screenings and film festivals, 1993-1995 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Miscellaneous screenings and film festivals, 1996-1999 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Miscellaneous screenings and film festivals, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Miscellaneous screenings and film festivals, 2001-2004 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Miscellaneous screenings and film festivals, 2005-2006 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Miscellaneous screenings and film festivals, Undated (Box 14, Folder 55)
- Series III: Publicity
  This series contains material related to the publicity of Paper Tiger TV. It has been broken up into two series. The first, "Press", is comprised of published articles, advertisements, reviews, etc. about PTTV. The second series, "Promotion", contains material produced by PTTV for distribution of their programming and other activities, and includes flyers, mailers, and schedules.
  - Subseries A: Press
    - ABC CLIO video reviews, Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - The Advocate and Greenwich Time (Connecticut), 1991 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Afterimage / AFI, 1983-1987 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Afterimage - on "Youth and the Media", 1990-1993 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Afterimage - "Mogul World Tour" - Dee Dee Halleck, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Alternative Media, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Alter Net - article proposal, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - American Film, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Art Com articles, Undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - ArtForum, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Art Papers - Virginia (Key Gallery), 1991 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Article dub masters, Undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Atlanta Journal, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Audio Visuelle Media - Rotterdam, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Austin Access - annotated, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - BRC News, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Brecht Forum 25th Anniversary Journal - Access Orbit advertisement, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - "California Student Ln." - publications with PTTV reviews, 1983-1988 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Camera Austria, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Check Point, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Cockburn article - Alternative Press Published, c. 1987 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Cologne, Germany, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Columbia Journalism Review, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - The Columbus Dispatch, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Com Pact, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Bill Boddy's article in "Communications" - Paris, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Community Media Review, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Complete Gulf Crisis TV Project set of articles (Dee Dee Halleck), Undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Crash, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Cultures in Contention, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Dallas Observer, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Days of Decision, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Deep Dish TV - with PTTV mention, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Deep Dish TV - with PTTV mention, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Dénonciation - French journal, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Discourse - on Born to be Sold, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Downtown Resident, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Downtown, 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - FFWD, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - FYI - Dee Dee Halleck on the Public Sphere, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Freeing the Media, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - From VTR to Cyberspace, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Fuse, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - The Georgia Straight, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Gramma (Cuban film/video festival), 1985 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - The Guardian, 1983-1985 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - The Guardian, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Gulf Crisis TV mentions, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Gulf Crisis TV newspaper clippings, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Gulf Press Copies, Undated (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Hartford Courant, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - High Performance, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Image News - Atlanta, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - ImMediaTe Impact, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - ImMediaTe Impact, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - In Pittsburgh, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - In These Times [and other articles], Undated (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - In These Times - on Dee Dee Halleck, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - The Independent, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - The Independent - GCTV, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - The Independent - mixed articles, 1982-1985 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - The Independent - Roar Review, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - International press, Undated (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Italian article, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - Japanese article, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Japanese article, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - Japanese mentions/ads, Undated (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - Jump Cut - Drawing the Line at Pittston, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - Labor Notes, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - Larsen, Ernest - article, Undated (Box 15, Folder 70)
    - Leonardo - by Dee Dee Halleck, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 71)
    - L'immagine Electronica, Undated (Box 15, Folder 72)
    - Madison Isthmus, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 73)
    - Marcus, Dan - on GCTV, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 74)
    - "Media Culture" - Cyberspace, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 75)
    - Media, Culture, and Society, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 76)
    - Media File, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 77)
    - Media File (San Francisco), 1991 (Box 15, Folder 78)
    - Media File, 1991-1994 (Box 15, Folder 79)
    - Media Impact, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 80)
    - Media Network Newsletter - "Mediactive", 1985 (Box 15, Folder 81)
    - Media Virus, Undated (Box 15, Folder 82)
    - Mentions - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 15, Folder 83)
    - Michigan Voice, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 84)
    - Minimal mentions, Undated (Box 15, Folder 85)
    - Minneapolis City Pages, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 86)
    - Minnesota Visual Arts News (Chomsky article), Undated (Box 15, Folder 87)
    - Mondo, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 88)
    - Mother Jones, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 89)
    - Munster show, Undated (Box 15, Folder 90)
    - Muste Notes, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 91)
    - The Nation, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 92)
    - New Age Journal, Undated (Box 15, Folder 93)
    - New Art Examiner, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 94)
    - New Socialist, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 95)
    - New York Newsday, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 96)
    - New York Press, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 97)
    - New York Three Freedom Campaign Newsletter, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 98)
    - New York Times mention, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 99)
    - Nikkei, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 100)
    - Nuclear Times, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 101)
    - Off-Video - Spain, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 102)
    - Peace Review - "Radical Uses of Public Access TV", 1996 (Box 15, Folder 103)
    - Peace Work, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 104)
    - People's Daily World, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 105)
    - People's Weekly World - article notice, Undated (Box 15, Folder 106)
    - Pittsburgh Post-Gazette, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 107)
    - Pittsburgh Press, Undated (Box 15, Folder 108)
    - Point of View, Undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Providence / The New Paper, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Providence, Boston articles, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Public Access articles - mentions, Undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Punk Planet - "Youth Media", 2001 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Radio Workshop article, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Randolf Straight Gallery article, Undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - The Richmond News Leader, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Saca News, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - San Diego Reader, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - San Diego Union - on Herb Schiller, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - San Francisco Examiner - articles, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - San Francisco Examiner articles, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - San Francisco Weekly, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Scan 17 (Verda Burstyn) Springfield Cable, Undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Scat Facts, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Screen - Bill Boddy [Alternative TV in the U.S.], 1990 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Sight and Sound, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Sightlines - article proposal, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Soho News, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - The Sunday Oklahoman, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Texte zur Kunst (in German), 1991 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Time Out NYC - Freeing the Media, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Tokyo Journal (in Japanese), Undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Transmissions, Undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - TV Magazine, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Twin Cities Reader, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - UC Video Magazine, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Union Democratic Communications, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Union for Democratic Communications News and Notes, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Up Front - "Use it or Lose it", 1985 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Utne Reader, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 32)